["Superman main theme" plays]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[whooshes]
[wind whistling]
[wheezing]
[coughs. sustained whistle]
[wheezes]
[distant rumbling]
[rumbling grows]
-[thump]
-[groans]
-Ow! Oh!
-[playful growling]
[shrieks] Stop. stop. stop.
[barks. chomps]
Stop. Stop.
No. Krypto. Krypto.
-[playful growl]
-Ow!
-[growls]
-[coughs]
-[grunts]
-[quietly] Krypto.
[wheezes] Take me home.
-[panting]
-[wheezing]
[grunts]
Home.
-[panting]
-[groans]
[Superman grunts]
[growls]
[barks]
Krypto.
-Home.
-[sniffs]
[rumbling]
[crystals crackling]
[barks]
[energy pulses. hums]
[Four] Superman!
[woman speaking Kryptonian]
[man speaking Kryptonian]
[whispers] Thank you.
No need to thank us. sir. as
we will not appreciate it.
We have no consciousness
whatsoever.
Merely automatons.
here to serve.
Meet Twelve. She's new.
-Hi.
-[giggles] He looked at me.
[Four] I put your parents'
message on to soothe you.
Thank you.
He finds it soothing.
[speaking Kryptonian]
[recording warbles]
[recording repeats]
The message was damaged in
transit from Krypton to Earth.
But what is there…
[speaks Kryptonian]
[Four] "We love you more
than heaven. our son."
[Jor-El speaking]
[Four] "We love you
more than land."
[whispering] "We love
you more than land."
[Four] "Our beloved home
will soon be gone forever."
But hope vitalizes our hearts.
-and that hope is you. Kal-El."
-[Superman. barely audible]
[Lara speaking Kryptonian]
[Four] "We have searched
the universe for a home"
where you can do the most good
and live out Krypton's truth.
-That place is Earth."
-"That place is Earth."
And the rest of the
message is lost.
[Five] Fourteen fractured bones.
Damage to bladder. kidney.
large intestine. lungs.
Our poor Superman.
[Four] With a healthy
dose of yellow sun.
we'll have him up and
at 'em in no time.
[rumbling]
[whistling]
[energy hums]
[shouts]
[shout echoes]
[Lex Luthor] Engineer. come in.
[Engineer] He landed
somewhere near here.
I can't see where.
[Luthor] Well. keep looking.
[wind howling]
[humming stops]
[gasps]
[shudders] Golly.
[sighs]
Sir. you are only 83% restored
to health. You must rest.
No can do. Four. I gotta
get back to the fray.
[Four] But this Hammer fellow
just beat you at full power.
Sir?
[rocks. crystals clatter]
What is this?
[servos whirring]
Krypto!
[thuds. panting]
What the hey. dude?
I-I thought...
You destroyed the whole...
Superman robots. I thought I
told you to keep an eye on him.
We feed the canine.
but he is unruly.
And he realizes we are
not flesh and blood
and couldn't. in our heart of hearts.
care less whether he lives or dies.
Stop. Krypto. leave it.
Ow. Ow! Stop. Ow. Stop it.
Krypto! Ow! Ow! Stop it. Stop.
Sit. Sit. Stay.
[sighs. exhales]
[Krypto whines]
[sighs]
[whooshes]
[sonic boom echoes]
The alien is on its way back.
-[cape whipping]
-[wind whooshing]
["Superman main theme" plays]
Your Superman has abandoned you!
The people of Boravia will not ignore
him inserting himself into our affairs.
[laser warbling]
-[Hammer shouts. indistinct]
-[man 1] Accelerate the portals.
Primed and ready.
T-Minus ten and counting.
[man 1] Buckle up.
we're going live.
Ten. nine. eight. seven. six…
Bravo. what do you
have on employees?
I'm inside Chocos.
Larry. No fatalities.
…five. four…
-Can't win 'em all.
-[woman 1] …three. two. one.
-Target in sight.
-[rumbling]
-He's back. Your 5:00.
-Copy.
12C.
18A.
34B.
98Z.
8H.
[boom]
74D.
[grunts]
44T!
[shouts]
[shutter clicking]
[people shriek]
-Reggie. can you watch?
-Yeah. yeah.
-[sirens wailing]
-[horn honks]
Yes! Yes. yes. yes!
It's like he knows Superman's
every move before he makes it.
He does. He's been
studying him for years.
He's developed over 2.500
fight moves for any situation.
-[sirens in distance]
-Superman!
[Larry] Bravo. you got him?
Malik Ali. a local.
[woman 2] Lex. we
have the Engineer.
[Engineer] The target has
led us to the ice castle.
The rumors are true.
I don't know how in the hell
this thing hasn't been spotted.
[panting]
Mierda.
Comms. two to one.
Hijo de…
Lex. the entire structure
has descended into the ice.
We have what we
need. Return to base.
[Engineer] I can
drill into it. Lex.
Your pride won't be making
our choices today. Angela.
Thank you.
We'll need more than
you when we enter.
Comms. one to two.
We've done what we
need to do. Wrap it up.
The United States will continue to feel
the wrath of the Hammer of Boravia.
It's me. Mali.
Once I gave you free falafel.
when you saved a woman
from being hit by a taxi.
Are you all right. Superman?
Mali. you gotta get outta
here. It's not safe.
You saved us so many
times. Now it's our turn.
[Hammer] This is
your last warning.
-[boom]
-[people] Oh!
[groans]
Maybe you shouldn't have done
that thing in Jarhanpur. Superman.
[panting]
[groans]
-Flawless. people.
-[laughing]
Way to bring it home!
[laughing. cheering]
[hooting. squealing]
[no audible dialogue]
[hard rock music]
[whirring]
[electrical pulse]
[man 1] Decelerate all portals.
-Ultraman's back.
-Ultraman!
[brightly] Ultraman!
You did so good.
[woman laughs] Yes!
[chatter and laughter]
Sorry about that. I'm so sorry.
Sorry.
-Morning. Nino.
-Good morning. Clark.
[man on tv] Do these
unelected met a humans
think they can dictate
international policy?
It's outrageous.
[Perry] It's a big story.
Put it above the fold.
That's where we put it.
-You're late again. Kent.
-Sorry. Perry.
-Hey. loser.
-Hey. Steve.
Hey. what do you got
against adverbs. Kent?
How are we supposed to know how we
feel when we read this malarkey?
In sports writing. you learn
the sentence is the modifier.
-Hey. Ma.
-"Ma!"
-Hey. Clark!
-[Pa chuckles]
Uh. me and Pa just
wanted to call
and say congratulations
on that front page.
Boy. that is something!
Hey. ask Ma if she barbecued
up any good roadkill lately.
-Shut up. Steve.
-Like. uh. possum or chitlins…
-What's that. Clark?
-[Clark] Sorry. Ma.
I'm just in the middle
of a big news day here.
What are chitlins?
Chitlins are intestines.
[Steve] Thanks. Cat.
You read this crud?
I thought it was great. Clark.
"Great"?
[chuckling] Yeah!
Front page! Big time!
Well. we don't want
to keep you. but. uh.
wanted to say congrats.
and tell you we're
thinking 'bout you. Clark.
-It's been a minute.
-Tell him don't be a stranger.
Pa says. "Don't be a stranger."
I. uh… Yeah. I heard him. Ma.
Yeah. okay I gotta
go. I gotta run.
Yep. okay. Love you.
So. this guy just flew into midtown
and started attacking people.
demanding for
Superman to show up?
Yeah. It's all
there in my article.
Then I'd actually have to make
it through your writing. Clark.
Knowledge is worth
many sacrifices.
That isn't one of them.
[Clark] Ha. ha. ha.
Very funny. Lois.
-Oh. my God.
-He's so fine.
Twenty-two people in the hospital.
over 20 million in property damage.
-It does make you wonder.
-Wonder what?
As great as he is. maybe Superman
didn't completely think through
the ramifications of
the Boravia thing.
If this guy is
even from Boravia.
[Jimmy] What do you mean? His
name is "the Hammer of Boravia."
Yeah. I doubt his parents
named him that. Jimmy.
We have no clue what his
actual goal was here.
I think it's pretty obvious the
goal was kicking Superman's ass.
Uh. he did... He didn't
completely kick Superman's ass.
[Jimmy] Pretty
thoroughly. Clark.
Show me! You show me
what ties there are
between Boravia
and this "Hammer!"
Yeah. see. Superman did say
he thought the. uh. Hammer
might be faking a
Boravian accent.
Superman said that?
Yeah. I interviewed him
right afterwards. Great guy.
You know. it's funny that you keep getting
all these interviews with Superman. Clark.
I don't think there's anything
funny about good journalism. Lois.
Uh-huh.
[Ghurkos] The relationship
between Boravia and United States
has been like iron for 30 years.
until Superman came along.
[Luthor] What you're
looking at. my friends.
is the most powerful
being on Planet Earth:
Ultraman.
You created this man?
Ooh. Check this
out. The Engineer.
A former special operative.
whose blood I infused
with microscopic machines
called "nanites."
which she can form into
anything she can imagine.
And. of course. you're familiar with
my flying armored forces. the Raptors.
All together. they're an unstoppable
force we call PlanetWatch.
More than capable of containing
any otherworldly threat.
[snaps fingers]
So you want the
Defense Department
to hire your met a humans
to take down the Kryptonian?
After Superman acted with violence
against our Boravian allies.
I think it'd be
worth considering.
Big Blue stopped a war.
Naive. maybe. but
well-intentioned.
Well. I don't know the intentions of
an unattended firehose. General Flag.
I just do what I can
not to be splashed.
-Mr. Luthor…
-The disarming Director Crawley.
[sighs] The country of
Boravia has purchased
over 80 billion
dollars' worth of arms
from LuthorCorp in
the past two years.
-And?
-And no one would profit more
from a war with Boravia
and Jarhanpur than you.
A cynic might say that having
Superman out of the way
might not be bad for business.
Well. what's particularly
bad for business is dying.
And I have a distinct feeling
that's where we're all headed
with the Kryptonian
running wild.
So we're gonna lock up
all met a humans now?
Look. other met a humans
aren't going off half-cocked.
interfering in foreign affairs.
They don't have... And
I have proof of this...
a hidden headquarters
in Antarctica
that violates 12
international treaties.
And they aren't aliens.
Shouldn't all that be
more than enough reason
for PlanetWatch to at least bring
the Kryptonian in for questioning?
Admittedly. I'm not comfortable
with a being from another planet
as dangerous as him on the loose.
But the optics?
Superman is popular.
Less so every day.
according to chatter online.
Not to mention the potential
risk of failing to contain him.
I assure you. Secretary.
we can contain him.
Yeah. they got this stuff. uh…
What's this Kryptonite
stuff called?
-It's called Kryptonite.
-Well. it kills him. right?
As far as we can ascertain.
there's none left on the planet.
I have a workaround
for that as well.
You know what? It
doesn't matter. Lex.
Because without solid
proof of malicious intent.
it's just not worth the risk.
[clicks]
[lock clicks]
[pots clatter]
[clattering continues]
[suspenseful music]
What are you doing here?
Three months ago. we
had our first date.
And so. to celebrate. I am
making you your favorite:
breakfast for dinner.
That's your favorite.
You love breakfast.
Yeah. for breakfast.
You love it for dinner.
[chuckles lightly]
-[chuckling] What?
-It was very funny today.
-What?
-It was hilarious.
the little back-and-forth
we had going.
Mm.
You giving me guff
for my article.
Jimmy was eating it
up. [loud kisses]
I wasn't acting. Clark. If you
keep interviewing yourself.
eventually people are
gonna figure it out.
But the glasses.
Yeah. they won't fool
everyone forever.
And ethically. these interviews
are hugely problematic.
I mean. y-you literally know
the questions in advance.
Okay. so I'll let
you interview me.
I'm pretty sure you
wouldn't like that.
Come on. Lois. I'm media savvy.
I can handle any question
that comes my way.
Are you being serious right now?
Yeah.
You'd let me interview
you as Superman?
Sure.
How about now?
Um…
[beeps]
[Lois] Ready?
Let's do it. Cronkite.
Superman.
Miss Lane.
Recently. you've come under
a lot of fire for
what some might...
I don't know if it's
a lot of fire. but...
It's a lot.
Today the Secretary of Defense
said he was gonna look into
your actions in Boravia.
-[exhales]
-That... That's funny?
It's not "funny"
funny. it's just. um…
I mean. come on. My
actions? I stopped a war.
-Maybe.
-Uh. not "maybe." I did.
Okay. How?
Well. Boravia invaded Jarhanpur.
and I showed up and told
them that wasn't right.
And?
And… smashed some
tanks and things
and a couple of planes
and some other stuff.
There were no casualties
and no significant injuries.
Did you interact at all
with the President of
Boravia. Vasil Ghurkos?
A very small amount.
What's a very small amount?
That was between us.
[beeps]
This is all on the record.
Yeah. but that conversation
was between the two of us.
Yeah. and I would
ask that question
whether or not I knew
the answer to it.
-Really?
-Really.
[beeps]
After I stopped the war.
I went to see Ghurkos.
Where?
In the capital of Luchebic.
at the Royal Palace.
And?
And I took a private
audience with Ghurkos.
How?
I flew him out to
the desert. and I…
And you…
And I placed him
against a cactus.
A cactus?
So… torture?
No. Not torture.
Its spikes were like…
not even that big.
What did you say?
I told him that if he ever
messes with Jarhanpur again.
he'll have to
personally answer to me.
What did you mean by that?
That if such events occurred.
we would have a more serious
discussion. that's all.
More serious than tearing
up his back on a cactus?
Ghurkos was gonna kill people.
You seem to keep
forgetting that...
So. in effect. you
illegally entered a country.
inserting yourself in the middle
-of an incredibly heated…
-No. no. no. Hold on.
-Geopolitical situation…
-Hold on a second.
…siding with a
nation. Jarhanpur.
which historically has not been
-a friend to the US…
-Jarhanpur has changed.
…against a nation that's
technically our ally.
and then threatened to
murder their head of state.
First of all. whether or not
Jarhanpur is an imperfect country
does not give another nation
the right to invade it.
Yes. but the Boravian
government maintains
they're freeing
the Jarhanpurians
from a tyrannical regime.
Yes. but you know
that's very silly.
I do?
The Boravian government. of
all people. is saying this?
Come on!
This is on the record. Superman.
Now... No. Now. see…
Now you're being
dishonest. Lois.
How am I being dishonest?
-What are you...? Stop.
-Where's the button?
You're being dishonest because
you know as well as I do
that the Boravian government
is not well-intentioned.
I think that's almost certainly
the case. but do I know that?
No. I don't.
Can we go on now?
Yeah. fine.
-I don't... You do it.
-I…
You think this is going well?
Do I think this
is going well? Um…
I think I'm doing a good job.
[beeps]
Superman. did you consult
with the President
before entering
Boravian airspace?
[sighs]
-No.
-The Secretary of Defense?
-Or any US official
before you took matters
into your own hands
and decided unilaterally
how to handle
this extremely
delicate situation?
Ghurkos and his goons
were going to kill people.
Yes. but the results
of you seemingly acting
as a representative
of the United States will cause…
I wasn't representing anybody…
…more problems around the world.
…except for me. and-and…
-More than a war that lasted…
-…myself and. and. and…
…between 12 and 24 hours…
…good. I don't know. doing good.
…and was just replacing
one tyrannical
regime with another?
Is that really how you feel?
I'm not the one being
interviewed. Superman. but…
I question it.
Yeah. I would question
myself in the same situation
and hold off a beat and
consider the consequences.
People were going to die!
[exhales]
Okay. I'd like to change
the subject. if I could.
Okay.
You've gotten a lot of heat
on social media lately.
I don't read that stuff.
Superman doesn't have
time for selfies.
-Third person?
-Hmm?
You're referring to yourself
in the third person now?
No. it was just a
thing I came up with
that I thought I'd try to
work into the next interview.
This is on the record. Superman.
Okay. well. not the
part where I said that.
-Yes. that part.
-No. that part was an aside.
That was off the record.
You have to say "off the
record" beforehand. not after.
Why are you being like this?
Fine. I-I won't write
that you spend your spare time
trying to think up soundbites.
Which are terrible. by the way.
-Social media.
-Yes.
As you may know.
or maybe you don't.
since you claim not to
read any of that stuff...
Very seldomly.
Maybe sometimes people
catch you reading it
and looking very upset.
Okay. well. you can't use that.
People on social media are
suspicious because you are…
…an alien. yes?
Yes.
I've been very honest about
that. From the beginning.
I come from a planet
called Krypton.
-Okay.
-Which is gone now. by the way.
Destroyed. Along with
all of my history.
My parents.
They sent me here as a
baby to save my life.
Here. where?
I'm not gonna say that. You
know I'm not gonna say that.
Okay.
What do you know about these
biological parents of yours?
Just that they sent me
here to serve humanity
and to help the world
to be a better place.
-They said that?
-They did.
They sent a message
along with me.
That message is
why I do what I do.
I cherish it more than anything.
Because you understand now.
there are an awful lot of
people out there maintaining
you're here for more
nefarious purposes.
Hashtag Superspy.
Hashtag Supershit.
Supershit!? Come on. Lois!
You know that one
specifically irritates me!
This is on the record. Clark!
-[recorder beeps]
-I didn't make it up.
It's what people on the
Internet are saying.
I'm gonna go.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Come on. Clark. Don't do this.
[Clark] I'm not doing anything.
No? No. that's not you.
packing up your shit
and walking out of an interview?
I'm not walking out
of an interview.
-I'm just... It's late.
-No. this is what you do
every time you're
faced with conflict.
-I'm not doing anything.
-You get mad. You pout.
-Then you pretend…
-I'm not mad.
-…like nothing's wrong.
-Nothing is wrong.
Look. I gave you a
nice. long interview.
Longer than I ever gave
myself. by the way.
Oh. you can time your imaginary
interviews with yourself?
That's a thing you can do?
You got a lot of good stuff.
Some stuff you can't use.
I am well aware.
I knew this would never work.
What does that mean?
[dishes clattering]
Lois?
-What does that mean?
-Nothing. I just…
I told you I wasn't
good at relationships.
[water running]
Okay.
[low music plays]
[engines whining. slowing]
The real Antarctica! [gasps]
So cool!
[exhales]
It was right ahead.
But how are we going
to gain access?
Oh. ye of little faith.
[rumbling]
Oh. wow!
[energy pulses. hums]
[Eve] Oh. my God!
[rumbling]
[parents' message plays]
Superman. I preemptively
put up the soothing...
Oh. my. I do apologize. but
this is a restricted area.
Wait. Can we talk...
[nanites clicking]
[whirring]
[groans]
[shouts]
[grunts]
[metallic warble]
[Krypto growling]
[Engineer growls]
[yelps]
[whining]
-[whining continues]
-[gasps]
This is what we came for.
Hopefully. there's
something on here
we can use to
convince the general
Superman requires
immediate action.
I can't stand the met a
humans. but he's so much worse.
Super… man.
He's not a man. He's an it.
A thing with a cocky
grin and a stupid outfit
that's somehow become
the focal point
of the entire
world's conversation.
Nothing's felt right
since he showed up.
I know. Lex.
I've sacrificed my own
humanity to help get rid of it.
Can you get in?
-[exhales]
-[nanites clicking]
Might take a while.
What if the Kryptonian shows up?
[Luthor] Don't worry.
I'm creating a… distraction.
[sirens in distance]
-[rattling]
-[growling]
[growling continues]
[nanites clicking]
-[gasps]
-What?
[Engineer] This message…
-[Jor-El speaking Kryptonian]
-…from his parents.
It's damaged. but there's more.
-[Jor-El speaking Kryptonian]
-It's…
I can recover the rest.
[message repeating]
[rumbling]
[message continues
repeating rapidly]
[Kryptonian message continues]
Whoa! Got it!
[man 1] Let it out!
[growling]
It's an awfully
small distraction.
It'll get bigger.
[barking]
[rumbling]
[roars]
[screaming]
[Superman] Get! Go!
[barks]
Get! Get outta here!
[whooshing]
[people shout]
[panting]
[ground crackling]
-[roars]
-[thud]
[people screaming]
-[squeaks]
-[glass cracks]
[straining]
[footsteps thudding]
[reporter 1] The giant animal
was first spotted
early this morning
in a Jitters coffee shop
about seven feet tall.
but it has apparently
been growing.
[screaming]
[people screaming]
[whimpering]
-Everybody okay?
-[roaring]
Hey. buddy. Eyes up here.
[roars]
[flames roar]
[whistling]
[roars]
[hyperventilating]
Deep. slow breaths. ma'am.
You're gonna be fine.
[cheering]
[power warbles]
[through megaphone]
Everybody. clear the area.
[roars]
He's just so cheap.
like. so obnoxious.
You know what I mean?
[male reporter chatter on tv]
[Cat] You can afford
$1.000 concert tickets…
Finally a bit of good news amid
the chaos here this morning.
The Justice Gang has
arrived on the scene.
That's Green Lantern.
Hawkgirl and Mr. Terrific.
They're funded by the
LordTech corporation.
Get him!
[flames roar]
[Superman] Hey!
[straining]
[shrieks]
[roars]
[computer chittering]
[shouting]
[growls]
Heel. boy! [grunts]
[groaning]
[spheres humming]
-What's the skinny?
-Its hide is tough.
but. uh. it's off balance.
I've been trying
to figure out a way
to get it out of here alive.
Get it someplace
where we can study it.
-Oh. come on. man.
-What?
Go for its eyes!
[shrieks]
-[shouts]
-[creature grumbles]
My knee! Guy. help!
I made giant oven mitts!
Good for you. asshole! I'm
getting blinked to death!
[metallic clink]
[roars]
[sound slowed. muffled]
[metallic clinking]
-[smashes]
-[shouts]
[grunting]
Come on. be careful!
-[electronic warbling]
-[roars]
[thumping]
[crowd] Oh!
Good gosh! There's gotta
be a better way to do this.
-[roars]
-[heavy footfalls]
[creature groans]
-[beeps]
-[explodes]
[creature wails]
[sighs. quietly] Come on.
-[groans]
-[screaming]
["Superman main theme" plays]
[news anchor] Authorities
are saying there haven't been
any signs yet of loss of life.
thanks to Metropolis
hometown hero. Superman.
but the damage to property
could be in the millions.
City spokespeople…
How's it going with that
guy you were seeing?
You were saying you
weren't sure about it?
Yeah. He's…
A little strange.
Ooh! Kaiju steaks
all around. huh?
I was hoping we could capture it
and take it to an
intergalactic zoo or…
[helicopter whirs]
…at least euthanize
it less painfully.
Come on. bro. Don't
be such a wuss.
'Ey! Just another day in the
life of the Justice Gang!
-[scattered applause]
-Not our name.
It's just a working name.
Could very well prove
to be permanent though.
-Probably not!
-Good chance though. I'm saying.
[laughing] You okay?
Everybody okay?
[Green Lantern] Just
like to say thank you
on behalf of LordTech Industries
for the opportunity...
[smacking gum]
Why is nobody clapping?
[murmuring]
Come here.
This has to be BS.
[scattered chatter]
[host] Well. they
couldn't be mistaken?
[Luthor] Oh. no.
Well. that sounds
very disturbing. Lex.
Twenty-eight of the
world's top linguists
have confirmed the translation
and 30 of the top
forensic computer techs
have confirmed the validity
of the footage itself.
Any chance they're mistaken?
Unfortunately. no.
-[host] You have the footage?
-Yes.
[host] Let's take a look.
[Jor-El speaking Kryptonian]
[male translator] We love you
more than heaven. our son.
We love you more than land.
Our beloved home is
soon to be gone forever.
[female translator] But
hope vitalizes our hearts.
and that hope is you. Kal-El.
We have searched the universe
for a home where you
can do the most good.
And live out Krypton's truth.
[male translator]
That place is Earth.
I don't get it.
What's bad about that?
[Kryptonian continuing. warbles]
[male translator] The
people there are simple
and profoundly confused.
Weak of mind and
spirit and body.
[Jor-El speaks Kryptonian]
[male translator]
Lord over the planet
as the last son of Krypton.
[Lana speaks Kryptonian]
[female translator]
Dispatch of anyone
unable or unwilling
to serve you. Kal-EI.
Take as many wives as you can.
so your genes and
Krypton's might and legacy
will live on in
this new frontier.
[Jor-El speaks Kryptonian]
[male translator] Do us
proud. our beloved son.
Rule without mercy.
But what about all the kind acts
Superman has performed
over the years.
saving countless lives?
No. He's grooming us.
Lulling us into complacency.
so he can dominate
without resistance.
forging a path for his
super-powered descendants
to rule the Earth.
I will not accept
that. Will you?
-You seem upset.
-[scoffs] I'm…
I'm scared.
I will admit that. I am scared.
Because who knows how large
his secret harem is already?
[breathing heavily]
-[muffled shouting]
-[knocking]
[muffled shouts continue]
[door opens]
[woman] Oh. hell no!
Let me in! I'm serious!
[warbles]
Dude. you got a secret harem?
No. Guy. of course I
don't have a harem.
If any of that message
is even remotely true.
then you are exactly
the kind of alien threat
I was commandeered by
the Green Lantern Corps
to protect this planet against.
-Back off. Guy!
-Oh.
-Make a move. Big Blue.
-[breathing deeply]
Guy. relax.
Was the message real or not?
[inhales] The first half.
The first half is… is real.
The second half was damaged
in the t-trip from
Krypton to Earth.
-So it's-it's gotta be doctored.
-No way. Clark.
I know these computer
forensics guys.
They're not gonna say it's
legit unless they are sure.
I'm so sorry. man.
but there's no way
that message is fake.
Where'd they get
the footage though?
[wind whipping]
Are you considering bringing
Superman in for questioning?
We're talking with the President.
and we are reviewing our options now.
I'm sorry. but I have
to go. Miss Lane.
[Lois] And if you did.
when would that...
You buying this?
I don't put anything
past Luthor. Rick.
But the message is authentic.
If the Kryptonian is a
danger. we have to act.
I was a big Superman fan.
I supported him all the
time online and stuff.
but now?
I mean. I hope he rots in hell.
I don't care. You're
supposed to get out!
[Perry] Get me some pictures.
[man] We have a deadline!
Where is he? Get there now!
Don't call me Chief.
Okay. I'm gonna do my job.
It's no wonder the Kryptonian
interfered with
Boravia's interests.
Boravia wants to save
the people of Jarhanpur.
And Superman wants to
keep them enslaved!
[chuckles] Also.
from what I hear.
he finds Boravian women the
most physically attractive
and wants to add them
to his secret harem.
-[chuckles]
-[press shouting]
I have a question.
President Ghurkos.
Thank you.
[in Boravian] That couldn't
have gone better. Mr. President!
You were so handsome
and dynamic!
Wonderful!
Very handsome! Very handsome!
Go! Leave me be!
[door creaks. closes. locks]
[beeps]
[heavy metal music plays]
[whirring]
We did it. Lex!
I wouldn't celebrate until
the alien is off the board.
Oh. here. I brought you a
donut. From Dough's Holes.
New shop in Park
Ridge. of all places.
The fake message.
a stroke of genius.
It's not fake.
He is here to kill
us. I knew it!
At Superman's fortress.
I hoped to get the knowledge
to help destroy him.
Little did I know.
his own parents
would be providing it.
Oh. [speaks Boravian]
Right? Yeah.
Been thinking of opening
one in my half of Jarhanpur.
-[servos whirring]
-[whoosh]
Four. Four. What happened?
-I tried to protect Superman.
-[exhales]
[electrical zapping]
How did Luthor get in here?
It's keyed into my DNA.
Must protect Superman.
[panting] Four.
I'm sorry. friend.
[panting]
Krypto?
[whistles]
Krypto!
Well. yeah. that's
gonna become...
-Lex. I tried to stop him.
-[Luthor] It's fine. Heather.
Superman. we finally meet.
-Would you like a coffee or tea?
-Where's the dog?
Dog?
The dog. Luthor!
You took the dog!
That's right. Eve.
get all of this.
-[Eve shouts]
-[grunts]
-Where's the dog?
-[Eve gasping]
I have no clue what
you're talking about.
[sighs] He's just a dog.
I don't know what dog
you're talking about.
[muffled in mug]
Ugly dog in a cape?
-What did you say?
-Hmm?
[gulps] I didn't say anything.
You heard what he said!
You heard him! He took him!
I mean. it seems to me.
that the only rabid animal
around here is Superman.
Ever since the discovery of
the Kryptonian's master plan.
he's gone off the deep
end. Thoughts. Chris?
Can't say I'm
surprised. Cleavis.
It's guys like this.
they always got
a whole bunch of
dark. ugly secrets.
[Cleavis] What do you
mean. "guys like this?"
[Peacemaker] Thinks he's
better than everybody else.
Makes this declaration
he's against killing people
unless it's
absolutely necessary.
[phone dings]
Really. dude?
It kinda sounds like you're
trying to make the guys
who are a little more edgier
than you look like jerks.
-Know what I mean?
-[Cleavis] Mm-hmm.
[Peacemaker] A lot
of these guys. these…
Heroes from the magazines.
-they're obsessed with me.
-[sighs]
'Cause I'm more
jacked than they are.
-They know they don't have...
-[tv clicks off]
[gas whooshing]
You have a dog?
No. not really. It's more
of a… foster situation.
[Lois] Cocoa.
You were out there helping them?
-[whooshing]
-[Hawkgirl shrieks]
Oh. no. that's just. uh...
That's just some
dimensional imp.
They've got that handled.
I was looking for the dog.
[blows thudding in distance]
You okay?
The footage is not what
it looks like. Lois.
Okay.
The ship my parents sent me
in was damaged in transit.
so I only ever heard the
first part of the message.
And I believed I
knew how it ended.
That my parents had sent me here
to serve the people of Earth
and to be a good man.
I'm not here to rule
over anybody. Lois.
I never thought you were.
even for a moment. Clark.
[distant screeching]
[sighs] Oh. that's really good.
[sighs] I'm sorry we fought.
Me too.
But we're bound to. though.
We're so different.
I was just some punk rock kid
from Bakerline. and you're…
Superman.
-I'm punk rock.
-You are not punk rock.
I like the Strangle-Fellows.
and the P.O.D.s and
the Mighty Crabjoys.
Those are pop radio bands.
They're not punk rock.
The Mighty Crabjoys suck.
Okay. well. a lot
of people love 'em.
My point is. I question
everything and everyone.
You trust everyone
and think everyone
you've ever met is. like…
Beautiful.
Maybe that's the real punk rock.
[chuckles]
Lois. what did you
mean when you said
that you knew this
would never work?
I don't know.
I'm gonna go.
The DOJ has a warrant
out for my arrest.
so I'm gonna turn myself in.
Wait. what? Why?
Maybe they'll take me
wherever they took the dog.
I don't know how
else to find him.
It's a dog.
Yeah. and he's not even
a very good one. but…
He's out there alone.
And he's probably scared.
-[hand lands]
-[exhales]
[warm. light music plays]
I love you. Lois.
I probably should have told
you that a long time ago.
[whooshes]
-[police radio chatter]
-[thump]
-[thuds]
-[grunts]
-Is that necessary?
-[restraint zips]
I'm coming in on my own accord.
No one read me my rights.
Courts decided those
rights don't apply
to extraterrestrial organisms.
Therefore. at this
point. Superman.
you don't have any
rights to read.
The government is
very well aware
of the potential
limitations detaining you.
so we've outsourced
your confinement
and your interrogation
to PlanetWatch.
PlanetWatch?
[whirring]
I'm sorry about this.
[engine whirring]
["Bring Me Sunshine" by
Sophie Madeline playing]
♪ Bring me sunshine
Bring me love ♪
In your eye ♪
[engine whirs]
♪ Bring me a rainbow
From the sky ♪
♪ Life's too short to be spent
Having anything but fun ♪
[wind whooshing]
♪ We can be so content If
we gather little sunbeams ♪
♪ Be light-hearted ♪
[slams]
♪ All day long ♪
Hey!
♪ Keep me singing Happy songs ♪
[portal whirring]
[slams]
[metallic clattering]
[Luthor] Twice in two
days. What a pleasure.
Luthor.
Your obsession with me is
getting a little creepy.
Don't worry. Tall. dark.
and Martian isn't my type.
-Kryptonian.
-Eh. same diff.
-[whirring]
-[gear clattering]
[Superman] Where are we?
[Luthor] A pocket universe.
I replicated the Big Bang with
a LuthorCorp mega-collider.
tearing a tiny hole between
the two universal fabrics.
I'm able to access it from
multiple dimensional portals
I've set up around the globe.
[whistles]
Rex. the met a human
known as the Element Man.
has been called into service
for a specific purpose.
He can metamorphose into
any known substance.
Even substances foreign
to this planet. like…
[cracking]
-[Superman grunts]
-…Kryptonite.
[gasping]
[reporter 2] Once again. Vasil
Ghurkos is sending troops
to the Jarhanpurian border.
[Jimmy] Superman's
been out of commission
less than a day. and already
Boravia's pulling this crap?
-Right?
-What?
Sorry. I'm trying to figure out
how Lex Luthor's
connected to all this.
How's that a mystery?
LuthorCorp sells arms to
Boravia. Boravia goes to war.
Luthor sells more arms
and gets richer than ever.
-[Lois] Nope.
-[Jimmy] No?
Uh-uh.
I have a connection at BodaBank.
Boda handles the transactions
between LuthorCorp and Boravia.
Yes. LuthorCorp sold them
approximately 80 billion
dollars' worth of arms.
but for those arms.
Boravia paid only
1.625 billion dollars.
So Luthor gave them
arms for free? For what?
That's the 78 billion.
375-million-dollar question.
Have you found out where
they're holding Superman?
No one in the government'll say.
Luthor seems to be working
to disable Superman
just so he can't stop the
invasion of Jarhanpur.
Why?
That's way too much sugar. Lois.
I party like a rock
star. choir boy.
Still can't hide the
taste of petroleum.
God!
[phone dings]
Lex is holding Superman
in a pocket universe.
A what?
I don't know what a
pocket universe is.
Neither does my source.
They don't know anything
about anything. really.
But for sure he's in
a pocket universe.
Who's your source?
I can't say. but you owe me.
Big time.
Like…
I can't even tell you how big.
I love you. Jimmy Olsen.
-I love you.
-Love you.
[phone dings]
[phone dings repeatedly]
[dinging continues]
-[steam hisses]
-[monkey cries]
Just my Monkey-Bots here.
farming outrage 24/7.
Trashing you online.
[weakly] Hashtag Supershit.
[shrieks]
[inhales] Krypto.
[Luthor] How do you
contain a super dog?
[panting]
[Luthor] You beam super
squirrels into its brain.
[panting]
We'll learn what we can.
Then we'll put the varmint down.
It will undoubtedly be painful.
[man] Mr. Luthor.
please! I swear…
[Luthor] This is our private
correctional institution.
Yeah. most cells are
rented out to governments
who want to keep
their incarcerations
of political agitators private.
Others are for more
personal transgressions.
Fleurette wrote a blog about me.
-[sniffling]
-There are few things I hate
more than petty ex-girlfriends.
You wouldn't be telling
me any of this if you...
If we ever planned on
letting you out? No.
[thud]
[Luthor] You'd be terminated
already if it was up to me.
First. the government has some
questions they want answered.
[brake squeaks]
[metallic clicking]
-[Luthor] Rex. Look who it is.
-[metallic clicking]
[baby whines]
-[door slams]
You be sure to keep
our guest in check.
Little Joseph certainly
wouldn't want it any other way.
[machine whines]
I'll be back tomorrow to
get the answers we need.
[low hum]
[people chattering]
-Hey. handsome.
-[men laughing]
-[men chattering. indistinct]
-[sirens in distance]
Come on over.
-Hi!
-Hey. Eve.
Oh. sorry we had to meet here.
but Lex is always
accessing traffic cameras.
so he knows where I am.
I really don't understand why
you stay in that relationship.
'Cause he made a point to tell
me about all his ex-girlfriends
he had imprisoned in
his pocket universe.
-What?
-Right?
-How's your mom?
-My mom?
Oh. I love her so much.
I think of her as my mom.
even more than my own mother.
Oh. she feels the same way.
from the-the one time
that you guys met.
-Yeah?
-So. hey. Okay.
-Yes. Yes.
-Eve?
There seems to be some
sort of connection
between Boravia
and your boyfriend.
-I'm not clear on what...
-Oh.
What's wrong?
-[sighs]
-What's "oh"?
I thought you wanted
to see me. Jimmy.
I do but. Eve.
how could I even really see you
with Lex still in the picture?
You're just trying to get
information out of me.
I swear to God. that's not it.
I-I just know that if I could
get some real dirt on him.
then maybe the
two of us could...
Could be together again?
[whispers] Yeah.
But you said my toes look like
someone spilled shrimp
cocktail on the floor.
You have unconventional
toes. Who cares?
There's other parts of
you that people would
find very attractive.
Lex tortured a
dog the other day.
-Jesus Christ!
-I know.
-I have to go.
-Eve.
Please see what
you can find out.
-[both whispering] Okay.
-Yes! Yes!
Okay.
I'm-I'm putting
'em in my pocket.
[kisses] Okay.
[cries]
[gasps] Joseph. He's your son?
Don't talk to me.
Please.
[gasps]
I could fly over and get
him if you just... [panting]
If you'd stop with
the Kryptonite.
There's no way out of
here. okay? So. just…
-There's always a way.
-I said don't talk to me!
[screams]
I told you.
[flesh sizzling]
Don't talk to me!
[heroic music]
[Guy] Yeah. so what
do you want me to do?
Where's the creamer?
[Hawkgirl] On the counter.
where it always is.
He's in your group.
right? The. um. uh...
-What's it called. again?
-The Justice Gang.
-No.
-We're not called that.
Yeah. your name is Mr. Terrific.
You don't get a vote
with a name like that.
I also voted against it.
Yes. And as leader.
I get tiebreaker.
No. Superman is not
officially a member.
Because you don't
want him to vote.
You know which
way that would go.
Shut up. He's kidding.
So. how do you even
know Superman anyway?
I… just… do.
So you know about
the hypno-glasses?
Now she does.
I'm not saying who he is. just
that he wears hypno-glasses.
They make his face…
Terrific. how do they work?
They make his face
look different
in your brain when
he wears them.
So that you don't
know who he is.
Yes. I know this. first of all.
But. second of all. you really
shouldn't be telling me this
in case I don't know who he is.
So. you know he's Clark Kent?
Oh. my God. Why does
he trust everyone?
He doesn't. Just us because
we are also of the cloth.
"Of the cloth?"
-What are we gonna do?
-About what?
Superman! He's your friend!
Some friend. Came
here to rule over me?
It would be difficult
to find him.
I put nanobot GPS trackers
into Superman's bloodstream.
You can see where his trail ends
abruptly right here
at Fort Kramer.
a dormant military post across
the river about ten miles down.
Even if he was dead. those
trackers would still be there.
So. all this leads
me to believe.
as your article surmised.
he really is in a
pocket universe.
[keyboard clacking]
You put nanobot GPS trackers
in your friend's bloodstream?
Oh. I do that to everybody.
So. okay. Come on. Let's
go to Fort Kramer then.
The four of us. and find
out what's going on.
And then do what?
Save him.
You wanna break a federally
incarcerated
prisoner out of jail?
Look. I think this is being done
to keep him from interfering
with the Boravian invasion.
No. you look. I'm a
Green Lantern. lady.
That means I took a vow not
to get involved in politics.
Oh. that's part of the vows?
It's implied. Yeah.
An implied vow?
Every time there's something
he doesn't want to do.
he says it's part of some vow.
Oh. I swear to God.
I am two seconds away from
forming a giant hammer.
and beating you both to death.
Is Supes here to
take over the world?
I don't know. Probably not.
But the risk is just
not worth the beef
between the US government
and the Justice Gang.
Not our name. Makes
us sound like cowboys.
But I agree with the rest.
So you're just gonna
let your friend rot
in a pocket universe?
[exhales]
[papers rustle]
That haircut should
be against your vows.
That what?
That what should be what?
I'll have you know 348
chicks say otherwise.
[alarm chirps]
Hey!
[wind whistling]
What?
I'm not saying we're
gonna save him. but…
…I think we can at least
check out what's going on
with your boyfriend
at this Fort Kramer.
He's not...
We're just seeing each other.
But thanks.
You want me to drive?
We'll take my ride.
[chirps]
[garage door whirs]
[Mr. Terrific clears throat]
You have a flying saucer.
but you couldn't get
a faster garage door?
I haven't worked on that yet.
I'm not even sure
how I feel. Honestly.
-What?
-About Clark.
He's not my boyfriend.
We've actually just
been seeing each other…
-Yeah. lady. just to be clear.
-…for a couple of months...
I'm not into people's emotions.
Yeah. no. totally.
I'm just thinking out loud.
I was gonna break up
with him. actually.
I mean. we had this huge fight.
and he told me he loved
me. and it just didn't…
[engine blasts]
-[Luthor] Q&A time. alien.
-[banging]
Today we have a special guest.
-[man panting]
-I'm familiar with him.
And the smell of his piss as
we flew across the desert.
That is a lie!
No. not Vasil. He's just
here as an observer.
[gasps] Mali.
Now. the US government has
a few questions for you.
Luthor. I barely know him.
He gave me food one time.
Who are you working
with here on Earth?
[barrel spins]
[Superman] I'm not working
with anyone. Luthor.
[Mali] Don't tell him
nothing. Superman.
I have no family or nothing.
Luthor. don't do this.
You eating my food was
a great honor. Superman.
[empty chamber clicks]
-Ooh.
-No.
-Got lucky on that one.
-[Superman] No. please.
[laughs]
No. Luthor. don't
do this. Please.
Let's try another question.
shall we. Superman?
-Luthor. don't do this.
-Who raised you as a child?
-I can't.
-I believe in you. Superman!
-No!
-Don't tell him...
[gunshot]
[body thuds]
[screams]
I didn't imagine that
would go so quickly.
[chuckles] I'm sorry. it's…
[laughs]
Mr. Handsome.
I'll be back later with someone
else you've chatted with.
and I'll kill them too.
Maybe that reporter you
always do interviews with.
Maybe I'll kill Clark Kent next.
[quiet crying]
[crying intensifies]
No. no. no. no.
[ship engine whirring]
["5 Years Time" by Noah
and the Whale playing]
♪ …over me and you ♪
♪ And there'll be
love In the bodies ♪
♪ Of the elephants too ♪
♪ And I'll put my
hands Over your eyes ♪
♪ But you'll peep through ♪
[engine slowing]
[stairs clatter]
♪ And there'll be sun. sun.
sun All over our faces ♪
[spheres warble]
[raptor 1] Restricted area. pal!
Get back to your vehicle
and get out of here!
[raptor 2] Whoa!
What do we got here?
[raptor 3] Hey!
You see this guy?
Unbelievable.
-[raptor 1] Hey!
-Um…
[raptor 3] You at the
wrong address. bro.
That's his path.
DNA trail leads to that tent.
[raptor 4] Keep moving. clown.
Isn't that one of
those Justice guys?
It's just the smart one.
Hey! You heard the man.
I am giving you one
last chance to stop!
I was just about to
say the same to you.
-[music continues]
-Fire!
♪ It was fun. fun.
fun Oh. it was fun ♪
["5 Years Time" continues]
[raptor 1] Fall back! Fall back!
Get out of the way!
Cover me!
[shouts]
Flank right! [groans]
♪ And she'll say ♪
♪ "Yeah. well. I feel
All pretty happy too ♪
♪ And I'm always pretty happy ♪
♪ When I'm just Kicking
back with you" ♪
♪ And it'll be love. love.
love All through our bodies ♪
♪ And love. love. love ♪
-[raptor] Look out!
-♪ All through our minds ♪
[blasting]
♪ Love. love. love
All over her face ♪
♪ Love. love. love ♪
♪ All over mine ♪
♪ Although admittedly
All these moments ♪
♪ Are just in my head ♪
♪ I'll be thinking about
them As I'm lying in bed ♪
♪ And I know that admittedly
It might not even come true ♪
♪ But in my mind I'm havin'
A pretty good time with you ♪
[panting]
[music continues quietly]
Holy shit.
["5 Years Time" fades out]
Unbelievable.
That jackass did create
a pocket universe.
[Lois] And that's… bad?
When creating a pocket universe.
if you are just one picometer off.
you will have a black hole
where Earth used to be.
And every time
you enter or exit.
you risk tearing a hole
in the fabric of reality.
You're kidding.
It's the type of
reckless science
Lex Luthor specializes in.
What are they doing?
[Mr. Terrific] They're
trying to hack it.
So. I guess you decided to help.
Only because it'll
piss off Green Lantern.
Thanks. [sighs]
[ragged breath]
[sobbing]
He just killed that poor guy.
[grunting] Mali.
His name was Mali.
And I didn't… I... I didn't…
[quietly] I didn't do anything.
You said you can get
to my son. right?
[grunting. panting]
[crackling]
[gasps. coughing]
[panting] Ooh.
[grunts. pants. exhales]
Why are you still gross-looking?
[exhales] I don't know.
I thought that…
It must be the sun.
What are you... What
sun? There's no sun here.
That's the problem.
I need to heal.
[grunts] I get my powers
from the yellow sun.
Just… give me a second.
Come on!
[whirring]
Hell. yeah. We're in.
[heavy metallic rattle]
[rattles]
Whoa! An anti proton river.
[rumbling]
-Do we rappel?
-Rappel?
Where am I gonna get
the gear to rappel
into a pocket universe?
I don't know. Maybe
it comes out of your…
Circles or something.
-Circles?
-What?
-T-spheres.
-Okay.
They're three-dimensional.
Circles are flat.
Sorry.
[scoffs] Unbelievable.
This place is filthy
with black hole vortexes.
and that anti proton river
will tear us apart in seconds.
We cannot go in ourselves.
Copy.
I can't make a sun.
I know.
I can only make something
kind of like a sun.
-What?
-All right.
Okay.
Okay. we got hydrogen.
and deuterium.
And we got helium.
-And compression. obviously.
-What are you doing?
Hey! Hey. no. no. Stop!
Enough! You're. you're gonna
get all of us in trouble!
Hey. bro. what are
you doing? Stop that!
He's doing something in here!
Guards! Guards! He's
doing something!
No. you are not going
to take credit for this.
I am the one that saw it first.
Oh. take a hike. Barbie!
-I'm getting the credit for it!
-Barbie?
These two are gonna
get us killed!
Guards! Guards!
-Raptors! Raptors!
-In here! Guards! Guards!
I'm seeing something
that you'd all wanna see!
[solar flames roar]
[T-spheres warble]
[energy pulsing]
["Superman main theme" plays]
[groans]
Joey!
[coos]
You have to take him.
I can't carry him
when I change forms.
[panting]
[boots squealing]
Whoa. whoa. whoa. No.
no. no! Krypto! Krypto!
-Stop! Krypto! Krypto! Stop!
-[whimpering]
You're gonna squash
the baby. Stop!
What do you see?
Did you find him?
Oh. my God! What is that?
Portal's been open too long.
We can't stand here much longer.
Aw. you look like shit.
I'm fine. [panting]
I think we need to get to
those portals up there.
Uh. right. How do we…
-[baby coos]
-…work them?
[panting] I don't know.
but we'll figure it out.
Yeah.
[thud]
[Rex] Joey!
-[grunts]
-[baby cries]
-[Superman groans]
-[baby whines]
[cries]
Kill him! He's still weak!
[shouts]
[shrieks]
[baby cries]
All right. freak. Nice and
slow. Back in the cage.
[bubbling]
What are you gonna
do. splash us?
[raptors laugh]
Yes. With fluoroantimonic acid.
[all shouting]
[screaming]
[weapons whirring]
[lasers blasting]
-[rock crumbling]
-[Lois grunting]
[panting] Do you have him?
-Hot damn.
-[Lois] What?
[Mr. Terrific]
It's a flying dog.
-Uh-oh.
-What?
[groaning]
Come on. come on!
No. no. no! No!
[laser blasts continue]
[raptor shouts]
[cries]
[Superman] Black hole!
[whistles]
[whines]
Oh. boy!
Krypto! Come here. boy!
I can't get out of this!
Krypto!
It's a black hole! We'll
never get out of it!
Pull us out!
Krypto! Come!
-[baby cries. coos]
-Stop it! Krypto! Help us out!
Bad boy!
Rex!
Joey!
[men straining]
[whooshing]
["Superman main theme" plays]
[grunts]
-[baby coos]
-[sighs]
Man. you are so weird.
[power hums]
-Do you have him?
-Them.
Superman. a mean dog in a cape.
a weird baby. and
a squiggle man.
What?
-Terrific?
-Follow me!
-[T-sphere hums]
-[barking]
[Superman] Krypto! No! Leave it!
[crumbling]
[whooshes]
[metallic creaking]
[Lois shouts]
[growling]
Are you kidding me?
-[growls]
-Those things aren't cheap!
[barks. growls]
[exhales]
[Rex] Oh. my gosh. Thank you.
-[coos]
-Hey. buddy.
-Hey. Hey.
-[panting]
-[weakly] You came to get me.
-Yeah.
-[Lois panting]
-[Superman grunts]
There's more people… being
held prisoner in there.
We gotta go get 'em.
-[Lois] Whoa.
-Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Not through here. you can't.
Not with you like this.
-[Superman panting]
-[Mr. Terrific] Clark. what the...
It's Kryptonite poisoning.
He'll heal. but it'll
take a day or two.
Get him someplace
safe. Take the T-craft.
The controls are
easy and intuitive.
I need to stay back here and
make sure the portal is secure.
-[thumps]
-[quietly] Okay… okay.
-Okay.
-[controls beeping]
Okay.
No. Dog? Dog. I
really need to...
No. Dog. I really need you to...
Come on. [grunts]
-Okay. Intuitive.
-[controls beeping]
Yeah. For sure.
[whirring]
Okay.
That's it.
[panting]
-[engine roars]
-Whoa!
[growling]
Pick that up!
[shutter clicking]
Eve! Get out of here. you idiot!
-Go!
-[grunts]
[Luthor] Move!
How the hell could he
have gotten free? Hmm?
[clatters]
[Luthor] We need to find him.
[phone vibrates]
Eve?
Oh. I'm so done. Jimmy. [crying]
Oh. um…
I have everything you
need to ruin Lex forever.
What? Where?
[gasps] Oh. I have
it right here.
How dare he throw
a pencil at me?
He's gonna regret harming
me for the rest of his life.
Such a jerk.
[panting]
But if I send you this. Jimmy…
[exhales] Uh-huh.
You have to promise me we
get to hang this weekend.
[sniffles] Just the two of us.
Uh…
-Okay.
-Yeah? Okay! Yay!
Uh-huh. How. uh… How long?
-All weekend.
-[shouts] All weekend?
[Eve] Oh. my God. Jimmy!
I'm sorry this is such a
major imposition on your life!
No. it's not an imposition. I...
I can tell you don't
really think so.
-[door slams]
-[screams]
-No. no. no. no. no...
-Eve?
Come on. Eve.
[whirring]
-[winding down]
-[Martha grunts]
I'm... I'm Martha. This is Jon.
-I'm Lois. Hi.
-[Martha] Lois.
Here. Son.
Hi. Ma.
Ma. they sent me here
to rule over everyone.
They sent me here
to kill people.
Clark. that ain't... that ain't…
[panting]
[warm. light music playing]
Is our boy gonna be okay?
Yes. Mr. Terrific says yes.
Don't mind him. Lois.
He's just a big ol' mush.
Especially when
it comes to Clark.
[phone vibrates]
[Lois] This girl is
obsessed with you?
[Jimmy] Uh-huh.
How do you do it. Jimmy?
Look. I didn't even
want to bother you.
but you told me to call
with anything I got. so I...
Yeah. but I thought you said
she disappeared off the line.
I don't know. She might have
dropped her phone in the toilet.
-She does that a lot.
-[sighs]
Well. I'm not really sure
that sexy selfies are...
Your hot ex is a genius.
-Hot?
-We have to talk to Perry.
I'll be there as
soon as I can. okay?
[raptor] Sending sexy selfies
behind the back of Lex Luthor?
She has to be the biggest
idiot in the world.
Lex. he just told you.
the portal was destroyed!
The dimensional
aperture is still there…
Syd. tell him!
…which we can open
remotely. so open it.
It is not… safe!
We can close the aperture later
by inputting the
coordinates. correct?
-Theoretically.
-Great!
If we can't find him.
we'll need to draw him out.
[alarm buzzing]
[typing]
But Lex. that could tear
a dimensional rift into
the surrounding area!
This is something you
think I don't know?
[rumbling]
-That shouldn't happen.
-Oh. you don't say!
-Can you… Can you stop it?
-Can I stop it?
[rumbling]
This is why you don't create
a damn pocket universe.
[Luthor] There. Superman
won't be able to ignore that.
Now we know where he'll be next.
-[birds tweeting]
-[rooster crows]
-[tail thumping]
-[Krypto sniffing]
[rooster crows]
[mooing]
[sniffing]
[barks playfully]
Thought you was
out here. [sighs]
Hey. Pa.
[chuckles] Never seen
you sleep that long.
Last week me. Ma.
Hector and them.
we took a drive to
Beerki's Burritos
down in Luttus.
Like the one that used to be
out by that old. uh. blue barn.
out on that I-9.
you remember that?
-Mm-hmm.
-Burritos still just as good.
That Louanne. she...
she seems nice.
-It's Lois.
-Hmm?
Her name's Lois.
But yeah. she's… she's nice.
But you don't seem
quite yourself.
Yeah. well. that message
that my parents sent with me.
I had never heard the
second half before.
Well. I'd say what you
wanted that message to mean
says a whole lot more about you
than what anyone
meant for it to mean.
Pa. you don't understand.
I'm not who I thought I was.
They sent me here
to hurt people.
Parents aren't for
telling their children
who they're supposed to be.
We are here to give y'all tools.
help you make
fools of yourselves
all on your own.
No.
Your choices. Clark.
Your actions.
That's what makes
you who you are.
I'll tell you something. son.
I couldn't be…
[sniffs] …more proud of you.
[sniffs]
[screen door creaks]
[Martha] Ol' mush.
Clark. there's something on
the box you might wanna see.
[reporter 3] And over
in Eastern Europe.
Boravian troops
gather at the border.
seemingly mere minutes away
from invading
Jarhanpur once again.
[reporter 4] Now. nearby
villagers are willing
and ready to defend
their country.
despite the exponentially
superior firepower
of the well-trained
Boravian military.
[people shouting]
["Superman main theme" plays]
[reporter 4] The
villagers cling onto
what little hope they have left.
as they're surrounded
by the military.
[reporter 3] Boravian president.
Vasil Ghurkos. says the invasion
is to protect the
Jarhanpurian people
from a tyrannical government.
Superman! Superman!
Superman! Superman! Superman!
[reporter 3] Without Superman
here to stop it this time.
the Jarhanpurians
don't have much hope.
I cleaned your boots.
I'll go get 'em for you.
[T-sphere warbles]
[Mr. Terrific] Superman.
We need you here
in Metropolis now.
I have to get to
Boravia. Terrific.
There won't be a
Boravia. or a Metropolis.
or a Planet Earth. if
you don't get here soon.
[rumbling]
This rift is about to
tear into the city.
I can't stop it.
I need your help.
[woman. through PA] All
Metropolis citizens.
-This is a mandatory evacuation.
-[helicopter blades whirring]
Repeat: this evacuation
is not optional.
This is a mandatory evacuation.
Repeat: this evacuation
is not optional.
This is a mandatory evacuation.
[horns honking]
[Steve] Yeah. I'm sure
she's scared. but find her.
Yeah. we're all equally scared.
Come on. just put her on.
Please. Juanita. can you
put Persephone on the phone?
Yes. she will care! Cats
know the sound of your voice!
So. I was able to connect
with our contact at BodaBank.
Luthor's been selling
arms to Ghurkos
for pennies on the
dollar for years.
-Why. you ask?
-I do ask why.
He did it in exchange
for half of Jarhanpur.
You're kidding.
At first. I thought Eve was
just sending me selfies.
But in the background
of the shots
are maps. contracts.
all kinds of documents
chronicling Boravia's agreement
to cede half of the
country to Lex Luthor
once the invasion is complete.
He wants to make himself king.
-King?
-King.
Should we really still
be standing here?
Lois. you got that flying
saucer deal up on the roof?
-Yup.
-Grant. Troupe.
-Come on.
-[Lois] Grab the board. Jimmy.
-How many does it hold?
-Five. or six. Six.
-Okay. Lombard. you too.
-[gasps] Oh. thank you.
Why the hell would Lex
want half a desert?
His cultish acolytes
believe he's gonna create
a technologically
advanced utopia.
Utopia?
There's a profit factor as well.
I mean. the petroleum
deposits alone
are worth multiples
of his investment.
[Jimmy] Whatever
his motives are.
we know Luthor did
everything he could
to ruin Superman's reputation.
[Lois] Eve's photos show
he was behind the whole
Hammer of Boravia scam.
[Jimmy] And all the
bots stirring up
anti-Superman sentiment online.
[Lois] Mr. Terrific believes
Luthor is also behind
the spreading rift between
universes out there.
All of it seems to be geared
toward stopping Superman
from standing in the way of
the Boravian invasion. Chief.
Call me Perry. kid.
Post the story. Fast.
[ship whirs]
-Buckle up. kids.
-Why don't I have a seat?
-Jimmy. will you transcribe?
-Uh-huh.
-[boom]
-[Steve shouts]
[thud]
[cement. bricks rattle]
[Steve] Oh. God!
[all shouting]
[engine whirs]
[Lois] The Daily Planet has
obtained exclusive information
proving that billionaire
Lex Luthor is in league
with Boravian dictator.
Vasil Ghurkos.
[rumbling]
Clark. are you close?
It's about to hit Metropolis.
and my codes are not
shutting it down.
Shit!
[rumbling continues]
[buildings crashing]
Uh-oh.
[screams]
Lex! The rift is almost here!
[Luthor] So slow it down.
[man 2] I can't unless I can
put the code in to stop it.
Hold on a minute then.
-We gotta go. man!
-Otis!
[squeaks]
[rumbling]
-[thud]
-[screaming]
[metallic rumbling]
Not sure where we're gonna
land when the world is gone.
[horns honking]
[rumbling]
[screaming]
[tires screeching]
[rumbling]
[engine sputtering]
[glass tinkles]
["Superman main theme" plays]
[rumbling]
There's a code to
close the rift.
but it's too
complicated to hack.
Luthor will have the
code at LuthorCorp.
Just give me a minute. I'll
get Krypto. and we'll go...
You brought that dog. man?
Yeah. I didn't... didn't want
him killing my parents' cows.
[sighs]
[clanks]
[Bravo] Go on wide.
[Larry] Wrong. Focus
on The Engineer.
-I'm on the alien. Larry.
-7R.
[shouts]
[metal clinks]
[saw whooshes]
-[laser blasts]
-[screams]
[screams]
It's not too late
for either of you.
[Luthor] 5A!
You don't have to
do what Luthor...
[yelps]
[zaps]
-[thuds]
-[grunts]
[whirs]
-[Luthor. through comm] 2X!
-[grunts]
[Luthor] Now.
Angela. as planned.
fill his lungs and kill
the son of a bitch.
[nanites chitter]
-[nanites clinking rapidly]
-[gagging]
-[metallic scraping]
-[grunts]
Can't he hold his
breath for over an hour?
Not without air in his lungs.
He'll be dead in minutes.
[woman 1] The nanites are
suppressing his optic nerve.
Sight and X-ray vision
should be completely muted.
Lungs breached.
-[beeps]
-Da?
[speaks Boravian]
[in Boravian] We will not sleep
until the street is flooded
with the blood of
every Jarhanpurian!
[nanites clinking]
[shouting]
-[whooshing]
-[whooshes]
[metallic scraping]
What's his game?
Using friction to
get the nanites off?
Doesn't matter if he
gets them off his face.
The nanites are
still in his lungs.
Engineer. Ultraman. keep up.
[gasps] We're trying.
[wind whipping]
-Maintain iOS.
-Yes. No shit. Larry.
Hurry.
[growls]
[wind whistling]
He'll suffocate any minute.
Engineer. envelop
him completely.
[shouts]
[nanites chittering]
[low warbling]
[whistling]
Wait! Wait. wait!
What is he doing?
[Engineer shrieks]
I won't be able to sustain
the impact at this speed.
[shrieks]
No. Angela. unsheathe! He's
the only one protected!
[shrieks]
[heavy thuds]
[sighs]
Entering the hole.
Infrared. please?
[computer chirping]
Switch to night vision.
Whoa.
[gagging]
[groaning. gagging]
[coughing. retches]
Her heart's still beating.
but she's unconscious.
Call in the Raptors.
[panting]
[thud echoes]
[Superman grunts]
[both panting]
[panting]
[sighs] What the hell?
That's right. Cloning you
was relatively simple.
All it took was combing the
aftermath of your battles…
[through comm] …until I
located a strand of your hair.
That's how you got into
the Fortress. [gasps]
You had my DNA.
Yes. but as is often
the case with cloning.
the match was imperfect.
He might be even stupider
than you. If that's possible.
But easier to control.
-3L.
-[Luthor] And stronger.
22K!
[blows landing]
[Luthor] 31D!
2A!
5B! 5B!
6K! 9A!
-[techs laughing]
-My brain will always win!
Brain beats brawn!
[people screaming]
[explosions bang]
[man groans]
[screaming]
[thud]
[rumbling]
-[grunts]
-[screams]
[groans]
[quietly] Superman. Superman.
Superman. Superman.
No matter what you
do to me. Luthor.
your plans in
Boravia won't work.
Oh. really? Why's that?
'Cause I called in some friends.
[Boravian tech] Mr. Luthor?
There is an anomaly
at the border.
[deep warble]
Sorry. kid.
Superman couldn't make it.
So you got an upgrade.
[upbeat rock plays]
[wind whistles]
[rumbling]
[Hawkgirl shrieks]
[men shout]
[in Boravian] Our forces aren't prepared
to deal with met a human anomalies.
I've sent the word to retreat.
Retreat?!
No! No! No!
We must get to the bunker!
The bunker!
[shouts]
-[shouts]
-[shrieks]
-[gunfire]
-[mace crashes]
[shrieks]
[shouts]
[in English] I know
you won't kill me.
You are too delicate and weak.
like Superman. [chuckles]
[scoffs] I'm not like Superman.
[shouts]
-[ship hums]
-[panting]
-It's perfect. Post it. kid.
-[Jimmy] On it.
I think you overestimate
the importance
of Jarhanpur to me. Superman.
That was just a bonus.
I'm not killing you
so the Boravian military
conflict can proceed.
I created the Boravian
military conflict
so I'd have an
excuse to kill you!
Once you involved yourself.
I knew I could easily get
our government's support
in nullifying you.
Why?
Because you're destroying us!
10Y. 13B.
[glass shatters]
-[screaming]
-[thud]
[screaming]
You're driven by envy. Luthor.
-You couldn't be more obvious.
-No shit. I'm not dim.
I'm aware envy consumes
my every waking moment.
13L.
[shouts]
I know when they mention
Galileo or Einstein
or one of these other twits
in the same breath as me.
I feel a tide of vomit
burn the back of my throat.
But at least Galileo
did something.
He wasn't some dopey Venusian
catapulted onto this planet.
just to have the
world fawn over him.
because his strength illuminates
how weak we all really are.
[gasps. grunts]
So. my envy is a calling.
It is the sole
hope for humanity.
because it is what has driven
me to annihilating you.
1A!
-1A! 1A!
-[blows landing]
-1A! 1A! 1A! 1A!
Yes.
[rumbling]
[chuckles]
Oh. what are you
smirking at. you idiot?
[sighs] Brain beats
brawn. [exhales]
Sorry. chum.
[whistles]
[sustained whistle]
[whistle continues]
No. no. no! No!
You watch him through
those? Tell him what to do?
Krypto.
Get the toy.
[whines]
Uh. thir-thirty-s...
Oh. the stupid dog!
-[Luthor] Uh…
-Charlie down!
[whoosh. thud]
[metal clattering]
[zapping]
-[stammers] 12C! Aah!
-Delta down.
36B...
-No.
-[Larry] Hotel down!
[beeps]
[groans]
-[Luthor] No!
-Bravo down.
-Bravo down!
-I just said that. Larry!
[groaning]
[groans]
["Superman main theme" plays]
-[indistinct]
-[stammers. shouts]
Alpha down!
Lex.
The Raptors have arrived.
[jet packs whir]
-Kill him!
-Good luck with that.
[teeth clinking]
[rumbling]
[lasers pulsing]
[all groaning]
[thud]
[roaring]
[grunts]
[clatters]
[straining]
-[bone snaps]
-[screams]
-[screaming]
-[rumbling]
-[bone snaps]
-[sighs]
[Mr. Terrific] Hey!
This ain't playtime!
Quit messin' around!
We have to get to
Luthor to stop the rift.
[weakly] I'm not messing around.
I'm doing important stuff.
It's gonna reach
Bakerline any minute.
There are people there.
[rumbling]
[people murmuring]
-We have to go.
-We'll never make it in time.
-It's almost here.
-We have to try. Come on.
-[inhales]
-[man 2] Lex!
I'm closing the freakin' rift.
No! They chose
him! Let them die!
-We'll close it from
the bunker -What?
…before it gets to
a city I care about.
[sighs]
Open the portal!
[zaps]
[panting]
Wrap it up. Let's go.
Safety first. people.
[Luthor grunts]
[man 2] Hey. Hey. The code
to close the rift is in here.
-I can help.
-I don't need your help.
I'm goddamn Mr. Terrific.
You piece of shit alien!
That is where you've always
been wrong about me. Lex.
I'm as human as anyone.
I love. I… I get scared.
I wake up every morning. and
despite not knowing what to do.
I put one foot in
front of the other.
and I try to make the
best choices I can.
I screw up all the time.
But that is being human.
And that's my greatest strength.
[sighs] And someday I hope.
for the sake of the world.
you understand that
it's yours too.
Oh. that's beautiful.
But none of this matters.
you patronizing clown.
The government gave me
the authority to kill you.
If not today. then tomor...
-[barks]
-Ahh!
[employees scream]
-[shouting]
-[growling]
No. no. no!
Oh. my... Stop.
Krypto. put him down.
-[shouting]
-[screaming]
[Superman] Krypto. drop him!
Krypto. drop him! Drop him!
-[thud]
-[people gasp]
[panting]
[sighs] Dude.
[keyboard clacking]
[computer chirping]
-[drive clicks]
-Got it.
[clicks. whirs]
[deep warbling]
Yes!
[laughing]
-[indistinct]
-[Cat squeals]
Mmm. [groans]
-Lex.
-What?
Well. this just in.
An absolute bombshell
from the Daily Planet.
Billionaire Lex Luthor
aligning himself
with a foreign entity.
believe it or not.
Luthor has been giving them
billions and billions of
dollars' worth of free weapons...
Lex Luthor has been working
covertly with Vasil Ghurkos
and the Boravian government
to overthrow the
country of Jarhanpur.
Luthor has been
giving them billions…
We've had Luthor on
this show many times.
Little did we know.
he was a traitor.
[TV anchors overlapping]
Seems like the one thing
conservatives and liberals
can finally agree on
is that Lex Luthor sucks.
[anchor] The whole world
has turned against Superman.
and we all owe him
an enormous apology.
He is. of course. the hero
we always thought he was.
[news anchors'
voices overlapping]
[cheering]
[woman] Thank you! Thank you!
[cackles]
That was sick.
Guy. maybe he should
join the group.
[scoffs] Please.
I mean. no offense. but that
creepy mug is what you want
representing the
Justice Gang? [scoffs]
Justice Gang?
That's a cool name.
You're in.
[sighs]
Come on!
[muffled reporter. indistinct]
[secretary] Glad
you're not concerned
about the met a humans. Rick.
'Cause now they're the
ones making the rules.
[light guitar music]
Everyone file. This way. please.
[man] Easy!
-Fleurette!
-Mom!
[chattering]
Oh!
[monkeys chittering]
Get his bald ass to Belle Reve.
[slams]
[taps on car]
[engine rumbles]
[grunts]
-[chittering]
-[barks]
[ship whirring]
[people chattering]
[Eve squealing]
-Oh!
-[grunts]
Now we can be together forever.
[sirens in distance]
Miss Lane.
[exhales] Oh. hi.
I thought I might
give you an interview.
I could fill you in on all
of the behind-the-scenes.
Sure.
I think that would be…
Great.
Um…
How about over here?
For an interview.
[warm. triumphant music plays]
Hey.
I love you. too.
[both chuckle]
How long have they
been hooking up?
About three months. I think.
Got this place cleaned
up pretty good.
Cleaned yourself up
pretty good. too.
-You think so?
-Yeah.
Think it gives you character.
Maybe one day you'll
give me a name.
Well. Four's a name.
So is Gary.
[crystal shatters]
-[items clatter]
-[woman] Aw. shoot.
Sir. I think your
cousin has returned.
[footsteps]
-Yup.
-What the hell. dude?
Why did you move the door?
-I didn't move the door.
-Where is my dog?
[grunts. whines]
-[zooms]
-[barks]
[giggles]
Okay. well. this is why
he has behavioral issues.
No boundaries.
-[giggling]
-[smashing]
-It's not healthy. is it?
-Mm-mmm.
[upbeat music plays]
Come on.
Thanks for watching him. bitch.
She likes to go and
party on other planets.
-Planets with red suns.
-Oh.
Because of our metabolism.
we can't get drunk on a
planet with a yellow sun.
If I had any emotional
capacity whatsoever.
I'd be concerned
about her partying.
Yeah.
Superman. would you like to see
the footage of your parents?
-He finds it soothing.
-Oh!
Yeah. Gary. that'd be nice.
["Punkrocker Feat. Iggy
Pop" by Teddybears playing]
♪ I'm driving to my star ♪
[Jon] Everything you see.
you're seeing for
the first time.
♪ I'm listening to the
music With no fear ♪
[Martha] All of this is for you.
♪ You can hear it too
If you're sincere ♪
Clark.
♪ 'Cause I'm a punk
rocker Yes. I am ♪
♪ Well. I'm a punk
You did it!
♪ 'Cause I'm a punk
rocker Yes. I am ♪
♪ Well. I'm a punk
♪ I see you stagger
In the street ♪
♪ And you can't
stay On your feet ♪
♪ And you're faking
In your sleep ♪
♪ You wish that you were deep ♪
♪ But you can't hear
me Laughing to myself ♪
♪ If you could You
would be someone else ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a punk
rocker Yes. I am ♪
♪ Well. I'm a punk
♪ 'Cause I'm a punk
rocker Yes. I am ♪
♪ Well. I'm a punk
♪ See me die on
Bleecker Street ♪
♪ I'm bored with being God ♪
♪ See me steering in my car ♪
♪ I'm driving to my star ♪
♪ I'm listening to the
music With no fear ♪
♪ You can hear it too
If you're sincere ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a punk
rocker Yes. I am ♪
♪ Well. I'm a punk
[music stops]
One. two. three. four!
[rock music plays]
♪ We're on a planet of our own
That we made from the bones ♪
♪ Of the ones that we KO'd ♪
♪ Oi oi oi ♪
♪ Gonna dig an early
grave For the daughters ♪
♪ And deprave them With
those depressing days ♪
♪ Oi oi oi ♪
♪ Ain't gonna take this
Ain't gonna take this ♪
♪ I am a hellion
The new rebellion ♪
♪ Say our name. boy
Just say our name. boy ♪
♪ It's the Mighty Crabjoys ♪
♪ Oi oi oi ♪
♪ I know you said
This wouldn't last ♪
♪ That's a voice
That's from your past ♪
♪ I don't listen to those rats ♪
♪ Oi oi oi ♪
♪ My mother says
That I'm a fool ♪
♪ Dad says Obey the rules ♪
♪ They can't see
This stunning jewel ♪
♪ Oi oi oi ♪
♪ Not gonna take this ♪
♪ We will not take this ♪
♪ We are the hellions
The new rebellions ♪
♪ It was your world. boy
Now it's our world. boy ♪
♪ We are the Mighty Crabjoys ♪
♪ Oi oi oi ♪
♪ We are the Mighty ♪
Whoo!
♪ Crabjoys ♪
Hmm.
What?
Yeah?
It's just… a little off.
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to take it
apart and put it back together?
No. no. no. no. I was just…
You just what?
Hey. man. I'm sorry. I
didn't mean to bum you out.
[rubble rattles]
I shouldn't have brought it up.
Darn it. I can be
such a jerk sometimes.
Tired of searching for subtitles?
Ray generates them instantly: getray.app